Mari Krishnan M

LinkedIn | GitHub | WhatsApp

Location: Sambavarvadakari,Tenkasi - 627856 Email: krishmarish777@gmail.com | Mobile: 6369091901

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled web developer with over **7 month's of experience** in **HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery**. I have knowledge of popular frameworks such as **React.Js** and experience with REST APIs and MVC frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript,HTML, CSS

Frameworks : React.js

Libraries : Bootstrap, Material UI, Redux, React Router

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Gitlab

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

November 2022 - June 2023

Remote – Thoraipakkam, Chennai, India

- Designed and developed dynamic and responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from frontend
- Improved website performance and speed through optimization techniques by 65%

Frontend Developer Intern

Fabevy Software Solutions

November 2022 - June 2023

 Assisted senior web developers in the design and development of websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React..Js

EDUCATION

Udaya College of Arts and Science

Nagercoil , India

B.Sc - Bachelor of Computer Science **70%**

2019 – 2022

PROJECTS

Portfolio Click Here

- Designed and developed a clean and modern website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript
- Optimized website for speed and user experience
- Utilized responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- · Deployed on GitHub pages via GitHub Actions

Business Website Html,CSS Click Here

- Utilized responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Deployed on GitHub pages via GitHub Actions

Business Website Html,CSS,Bootstrap Click Here

- Utilized responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Deployed on GitHub pages via GitHub Actions

Magic Bricks CloneReact. Js, ReduxClick Here

- Designed and developed a clean and modern website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript
- · Optimized website for speed and user experience
- Utilized responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Deployed on GitHub pages via GitHub Actions

CERTIFICATIONS

• Certified Web Developer by the Fabevy Technologies